emetrics.org 2012-09-20

# eMetrics Marketing Optimization Summit, International Web Analytics Conferences

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to ensure that eMetrics Marketing Optimization Summit (we) interact with all of our customers in line with current legislation and in accordance with their wishes. If you have any concerns with how your personal data may be being used please contact us at [enquiries@emetrics.org](mailto:enquiries@emetrics.org).

We collect personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site. This information is used solely for internal marketing purposes and for the production of whichever event you have registered for. The only occasion when personally identifiable information is shared with third parties is when particular event attendee lists are made available to other attendees and sponsors of the same event.

## Orders

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email and office address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

We use this information for invoicing purposes and to fulfill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

## Special Offers and Updates

We will occasionally send you information on eMetrics Marketing Optimization Summit and/or other related events or products.

## Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable):

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.

### Personally identifiable information:

We only share personally identifiable information with Third Parties when particular event attendee lists are made available to other attendees and sponsors of the same event.

## Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. 

We use a third-party tracking service called Google Analytics that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate, including source, usage and frequency data to further improve our marketing effectiveness.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s "help" file.

## Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by eMetrics Marketing Optimization Summit. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [enquiries@emetrics.org](mailto:enquiries@emetrics.org).

## Business Transitions

In the event eMetrics Marketing Optimization Summit goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

## Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
